<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!--         LESSON 1            -->
    <string name="C4L1S1">Water is a substance that is made up of <b>atoms</b>. The atoms that make up water are 2 Hydrogen and 1 Oxygen, which is written as H2O.</string>
    <string name="C4L1S2" > When the atoms combine together, they become a <b>molecule</b>, it\'s often referred to as the "Mickey Mouse Molecule".</string>
    <string name="C4L1S3"><b>Phases of Water</b> \n Water can exist as one of three phases: solid, which is ice; liquid, which is water; and gas, which is water <b>vapor</b>, which you can see in steam or clouds.</string>
    <string name="C4L1S4"><b>Water Properties</b> \n Not only can water be found in different phases, but it is also known as the \'<b>universal solvent.</b>\' A solvent is a substance that dissolves (or breaks down) another substance. No other substance can dissolve as many things as water.</string>
    <!--         LESSON 1            -->



    <!--         LESSON 2            -->
    <string name="C4L2S1">Everything in the world, even the world itself, is composed of elements. There are four major elements that make up the majority of living things: carbon, oxygen, nitrogen and hydrogen.</string>
    <string name="C4L2S2">These four elements enjoy linking up through chemical bonds. A <b> chemical bond</b> is a bond that holds two or more elements together to form a molecule. </string>
    <string name="C4L2S3">Organic chemistry is the study of elements made of carbon-containing molecules and the bonds between the elements within a molecule. </string>
    <string name="C4L2S4">Capital letters are used to represent the elements. For example, N for nitrogen and C for carbon. Lines are used to represent the bonds.</string>

    <!--         LESSON 2            -->


    <!--         LESSON 3            -->
    <string name="C4L3S1">Food chemistry involves studying the chemicals that are inside food, how they contribute to our nutrition, and how different foods can be combined or changed to make new foods. </string>
    <string name="C4L3S2">
    <item><b>Food Chemistry Applications</b> Through food chemistry we can understand a lot about the foods we eat. Here are a few ways that food scientists may use food chemistry:</item>
    <item>To understand nutritional values of food. For example, are apples a healthy food to eat?</item>
    <item>To make new foods, like snacks, yogurt, gum, ice cream, cereal, soft drinks, juices, and more.</item>
</string>
    <string name="C4L3S3">Carbohydrates are great energy sources for humans and animals too.Table sugar is an example of a carbohydrate. Pizza, bread, and pasta are all examples of foods that are high in carbohydrates.</string>
    <string name="C4L3S4">Lipids are the fats and oils that come from plants and animals.Fats usually come from animals like beef, chicken, and fish; while oils come from plants like olives and sunflower seeds.</string>
    <string name="C4L3S5">Protein is an important chemical to the human diet. Protein can come from meat, fish, nuts, dairy, vegetables, oils, and nuts. </string>
    <!--         LESSON 3            -->


    <!--         LESSON 4            -->
    <string name="C4L4S1">Atoms are the smallest building blocks of matter. Atoms fit together to form larger structures called molecules. Certain molecules are known as <b>polymers</b>, and they play a large part in your everyday life. </string>
    <string name="C4L4S2">In the world of molecules, polymers are so huge that they can be made of thousands or even millions of atoms. However, what makes polymers unique is that they are made of smaller units of atoms that repeat. These smaller units are called <b>monomers</b>. In fact, the word "polymer"" has a hidden meaning. ""Poly"" means many, and "mer" means part.</string>
    <string name="C4L4S3">Polymers are a part of your everyday life. That\'s because plastic is made of synthetic polymers. Plastic toys, dishes, milk jugs and water bottles are all made from polymers. So is nylon, Styrofoam, carpet fiber and rubber bands.</string>
    <!--         LESSON 4            -->


    <!--         LESSON 5            -->
    <string name="C4L5S1"><b>Forensic</b> chemistry is the use of chemistry to help solve crimes. When a crime is committed, clues are always left behind . All the clues, either seen or unseen, can be analyzed by a forensic chemist, usually in a laboratory.</string>
    <string name="C4L5S2">Forensic chemists can analyze one strand of hair and tell whether it is human or animal, and the color or chemical composition of it.</string>
    <string name="C4L5S3">Sometimes the hair will even reveal the <b>DNA</b>, a large molecule whose information is unique to each person, of the individual whose head it came from! This type of evidence is called <b>trace evidence</b> .</string>
    <string name="C4L5S4">Chemists would test the unknown liquid using chromatography, or separating out the mixture of chemicals within the liquid or gas to identify it.</string>
    <string-array name="C4L5S1E1M">
        <item>Forensic chemistry analyze only unseen clues.</item>
        <item>True</item>
        <item>False</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="C4L5S3E2M">
        <item>Chemists would test the unknown liquid using ___?</item>
        <item>Chromatography</item>
        <item>Glowmatography</item>
        <item>Affinity chromatography</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="C4L5A">
        <item>False</item>
        <item>Chromatography</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--         LESSON 5            -->


</resources>